skfjkhcdcsh.com 2011-05-23

# AVG Worldwide - Privacy Policy

## Commitment to Privacy

As a security software producer, AVG Technologies knows that you care about how your information is used and shared. We respect your right to privacy. We want to make sure that you understand the type of information we collect about you, how it is used and the safeguards we use to protect it. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, AVG Technologies shall mean AVG Technologies CZ, s.r.o. or any other company controlled by, controlling or under common control with AVG Technologies.

## What Information Does AVG Technologies Collect? 

The type of information that we collect and retain depends upon your interaction with our Site. Here is a short overview of the two main types of interactions.

## Information You Give Us.

We collect the personally identifiable information you provide to us on our Site, including your name, address, email address, telephone number, and if you pay by credit card, your account information. This happens when you:

  * Create a user account, place an order, register a product
  * Requesting product support or other services
  * Request information about AVG products or services
  * Participate in surveys

Our products can collect information about your PC, about files or applications you have and sites you have accessed when they identify threats or potential threats. This information, with your consent is transmitted back to AVG. It is possible that on rare occasions this may provide personal information. Be assured we a) never use this data for anything and b) as soon as we identify it as personal information, we seek to delete it from our systems as quickly as possible.

You have the final decision on whether to proceed with any activity that requests personal information.

## Information Collected and Stored Automatically.

When you interact with AVG Technologies products or Sites we may maintain a record of the following types of information.

  * Your Internet Protocol ("IP") address or other technical information such as a referring web site, if any, and the path you take through AVG Technologies Sites when you visit us online.
  * The date and time, the internet address of the website from which you link directly to our website.
  * The name of the file or the words you search, and the browser you use to access our website.
  * Information about malicious applications, files and other potential threats on your computer, their behavior and origin
  * Files and the content of files that contain threats or potential threats
  * Information about your PC and the types and number of files and programs so that, where appropriate, AVG can suggest other products or services, including third party products and services, that you may find useful

The information collected and stored automatically by our Site is used to measure the number of visitors to our Site and to identify system performance or for server issues. We also use this information to help us expand the coverage of our Site and to make our Site more useful.

## Do We Use Cookies?

_“Cookies”_ are small pieces of unique information, sent by a website, that are stored on your computer’s hard drive by your web browser. Cookies enable a website to tailor information presented to you based on your browsing preferences. AVG Technologies uses cookies to personalize your pages at our Site, when you seek service & support or to remember you when you register for products or services.

AVG Technologies may also use cookies to track your visit to our Site. While our web servers may automatically log your IP address, the type of information we collect pertains to how you navigate, browse and purchase on our Site.

If you do not want us to store this information the _“Help”_ facility on your browser will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies or notify you when you receive a new cookie or how to disable cookies altogether. However, rejecting cookies may affect your ability to use some of the products and/or services at our Site.

## How Do We Use the Information We Collect? 

The personal information we collect is generally used to process your requests and transactions, to provide you with high quality service, to tell you about opportunities we think will be of interest to you, to customize your experience on our Site and to understand your needs so that we may provide you with the most suitable products and services. For example, we may use your personal information to help us:

  * Provide you with information about virus alerts, product upgrades, new products, services, research on future product ideas or improvements;
  * Send newsletters, informative e-mails or other information which has the nature of business announcements.
  * Create content that is relevant to you;
  * Provide you with special offers that may be of interest to you, including offers relating to third party products and services;
  * Assist us in creating better, customized products and services to meet your needs; 
  * Allow you to purchase and download products, obtain access to services or otherwise engage in activities you select;
  * Help you quickly find software, services, or product information important to you; 
  * Allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you chose to do so; and
  * Notify you about changes to our service.
  * Provide you with information about virus alerts, product upgrades, new products, services, research on future product ideas or improvements;
  * In case of your files, applications or emails that are malicious, potentially malicious or spam, this information is used ONLY to help us and our suppliers to improve the products

## With Whom Do We Share Your Information? 

### AVG Technologies Worldwide Offices 

Since AVG Technologies is a global company, we provide information on users of AVG Technologies’ products to our worldwide offices (subsidiaries and affiliates) which are listed at [www.avg.com/contacts](http://www.avg.com/ww-en/contacts). The personal information that you have provided to us may be made accessible to these AVG Technologies offices for marketing and customer relationship management purposes.

### Third Parties

AVG Technologies does not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to third parties. AVG, like all major organizations, uses a range of third parties to provide services to AVG and to you – either directly or indirectly. All of these companies comply with our Privacy and data security policies and we go to great lengths to ensure that they do not compromise your personal data.

### Selected Partners, Distributors and Resellers:

We may share your personal information, such as your e-mail contact, with selected AVG Technologies partners, distributors and resellers so that they can contact you, either on our behalf or for their own account, about products, services or offers that we believe are important to you or your business, or to fulfill any terms under your licensing and service relationship with AVG, and to provide you a local technical and customer support.

We may share your personally identifiable information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is: a) authorized by law or necessary to comply with a legal process or to deliver the product or service you require; b) in response to legal claims; c) required to protect and defend the rights, property or legitimate interests of AVG Technologies; d) necessary to protect personal safety, property or other rights of AVG Technologies and its customers or employees; or e) an integral part of a sale of all or part of our business.

## Consent

When you gave us your information you will have been asked to tell us how you would like us to use your personal data. And you will have seen a link to this Privacy Policy. You can change that consent at any time, by contacting [privacy@avg.com](mailto:privacy@avg.com) and requesting whatever change you require. We will do our best to comply with request as quickly as possible.

## Security

AVG Technologies is committed to maintaining the security of information under our control. We have taken security measures, consistent with best industry practices, to protect your personal information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information, we have put in place industry-accepted physical, technical and administrative practices to safeguard and secure the information we collect.

## How Can You Correct Inaccuracies in the Information? 

### Registration

We strive to maintain the accuracy of the information collected through our Site. We will provide you with access to personally identifiable information you provide through our Site for as long as we maintain that information in a readily accessible format. Similarly, we encourage you to correct inaccuracies in the information you submit to us through our Site. If you believe that the personal information you provided to AVG Technologies is not up to date, you can update it by contacting AVG Customer services at [www.avg.com/support-new](http://www.avg.com/ww-en/support-new).

If you have provided personal information to AVG Technologies you may ask us to advise you of the scope of information AVG Technologies processes about you, the purpose and nature of the processing and the recipients of the information. You can do this by emailing [privacy@avg.com](mailto:privacy@avg.com).

## AVG Update Bulletin and Other Communications

Some AVG products enable AVG to transmit product and important service messages to your PC when you are connected to the AVG Server.

If you do not wish to continue receiving our e-mail newsletters, bulletins, or other information from AVG Technologies, you can opt-out at any time by responding to any e-mail you receive from us and writing the word “unsubscribe” in the subject line of the response. Please be aware that our e-mails may include important or useful information about your product, including information about your License Number or the status of your orders or accounts.

## Links to Other Companies

Periodically, our Site may contain links to and from websites of our business partners, distributors, resellers, advertisers or other third parties. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies which you should read before you submit any personal data to these websites.

## Co-branded Websites

We may also link to co-branded websites that are maintained by AVG Technologies and one or more of our business partners.

## Changes of Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. However, we will alert you that changes have been made by indicating at the top of the Privacy Policy the date it was last updated. If we ever make a material change to how we use the information you provide and the new uses are unrelated to uses we disclose in this Policy, we will communicate the changes by email to you and provide you the opportunity to change your marketing preferences to opt-out of such use.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please email us at [privacy@avg.com](mailto:privacy@avg.com).

This website is maintained by AVG Technologies CZ, s.r.o. in Brno, the Czech Republic. AVG Technologies CZ, s.r.o. is a data collector. End user data may be considered personal information pursuant to the Czech Act no. 101/2000 Coll., on the protection of personal information, as amended, or under any other applicable relevant legislation.

Last Updated 27 October 2010
